https://www.midwestsports.com/privacy-policy/a/privacypolicy/

Racquet Specials
Shop By:
Court Maintenance
Court Supplies Nets & Posts Windscreens Clay Courts Court Resurfacing Shop Gift Cards
Sale Tennis Shoes
Shop By:
Women's Styles
Women's Tennis Bags Cool Weather Gear Training Apparel Plus Sizes WTA Pro Player Gear Hats, Caps, Visors Headbands & Wristbands Undergarments Socks Shop Gift Cards
Nike Tennis
Men'sTennis
Men's Tennis Shoes
Shop All Brands
Nike
adidas
Asics
Babolat
Sale Tennis Shoes
Shop By:
New Tennis Shoes
Clay Court Shoes
Warranty Shoes
Running Shoes
Wide Width Shoes
Socks
Men's Apparel
Shop All Brands
Men's Styles
ATP Pro Player Gear Cool Weather Gear Training Apparel Hats, Caps, Visors Wristbands & Headbands Socks Shop Gift Cards
Nike Tennis
Kids'Tennis
Shop All Kids Tennis
Boy's Boy's Tennis Apparel Boy's Tennis Shoes Sale Boy's Apparel Sale Boy's Shoes
Girl's Girl's Tennis Apparel Girl's Tennis Shoes Sale Girl's Apparel Sale Girl's Shoes
Junior Racquets
Junior Balls/Nets
Junior Racquet Guide Shop Gift Cards
Junior Equipment
TennisShoes
Women's Tennis Shoes
Shop All Brands
Nike
Sale Tennis Shoes
Shop By:
New Tennis Shoes
Wide Width Shoes
Clay Court Shoes
Warranty Shoes
Running Shoes
Men's Tennis Shoes
Shop All Brands
Nike
Sale Tennis Shoes
Shop By:
New Tennis Shoes
Wide Width Shoes
Clay Court Shoes
Warranty Shoes
Running Shoes
Kids' Tennis Shoes
Boy's Tennis Shoes Sale Boy's Shoes
Girl's Tennis Shoes Sale Girl's Shoes
Web Site Security
Our customers' security is very important to us.
We have incorporated SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology to our online ordering process through VeriSign RSA/Secure Server. This ensures that any credit card or address information entered on our site is encrypted and transferred to our mainframe safely.
PLEASE NOTE:
This site only becomes secure once you click on Check Out, located on any product page, and you begin to enter your personal and credit card information. All information (related to your order) entered after that becomes encrypted for your safety.
Customer Privacy
Midwest Sports Supply will not rent or sell your name, address, phone number, email address, credit card information, or any other personal information to any third party, PERIOD. However, we must cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.
By visiting our site, third parties may place cookies on your browser for targeted advertising purposes.
This data may be used by third parties to target advertising on other sites based on your online activity.
We also engage a third-party partner for the purpose of identifying users and delivering to them marketing on our behalf (i.e. email or direct mail). Our partners may collect information directly from your device, such as your IP address, device ID, and information about your browser or operating system; may combine personal and non-personal information about you with information from other sources; and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. This activity enables them to identify you to facilitate the delivery of marketing on our behalf. To opt out of recognition services, please go to https://idx.listrakbi.com/opt-out.html. To opt out of third-party cookies, please go to https://www.aboutads.info/choices.
Instructions on how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising by going to one of the following:
DAA
NAI
Europe EDAA
TOLL FREE: 1-800-334-4580
LOCAL: 513-956-4900
FAX: 513-956-4910
WEB: www.midwestsports.com
E-MAIL: info@midwestsports.com
STORE HOURS: Monday-Friday: 10:00am - 6:00pm EST
Saturday: 10:00am - 6:00pm EST
Sunday: 11:00am - 5:00pm EST
BUSINESS HOURS:
Monday: 9:00AM-9:00PM
Tuesday-Friday: 9:00AM-8:00PM
Saturday: 10:00AM-6:00PM
Sunday: 11:00AM-5:00PM
(All hours are Eastern Standard Time)
How Can We Help Learning Center Contact Us Careers UPS Tracking Returns Warranty Info Shipping & International FAQ Privacy Notice Do Not sell My Personal Information Mobile Site Sitemap
Categories Racquets Tennis Shoes Tennis Apparel Tennis Bags New Products Top Brands Gift Card
Sale Categories Sale Tennis Racquets Sale Tennis Shoes Sale Tennis Apparel Sale Tennis Bags Sale Tennis Accessories
Subscribe to us
Get Social
How SSL Secures You
© 2020 Midwest Sports
This website sets cookies on your device in order to give you the best experience. Without cookies, this site will not function as expected. If you want to learn more, please read our Privacy Notice. By closing this message or interacting with our site, you consent to the use of cookies on this device.
Close Cookie Consent Notice
